A Finding Aid to the Howard Wise Gallery Records, 1943-1989, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
- Correspondence, 1943-1984; Series 1; Archival Resource Key; 2 Linear feet Boxes 1-2
  - Correspondence, A-Z, 1943-1967; 1.1; Archival Resource Key
    - Kane, Michael - KYW Television, 1973; 1957-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 28)
      KLH Research
      Knox, Seymour H.
      Kootz, Samuel
      Kornbluh, Edward C.
      Krakower, Arnold
      Kramer, Hilton
      Krannert Art Museum ( see: University of Illinois)
      Kronick, William
      Krotinger, Myron N.
      Kryl, Bohumir
      Kulicke Frames, Inc.
      Kunstsammlung Nordhein-Westfalen
      KYW Radio
      KYW Television
    - La Hume Galerie, 1957-1963; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Lakewood Art League - Lerner Publications, 1952-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 30)
      Lakewood Art League
      Lambert, J. O.
      Landor, Walter and Associates
      Lang, Fran and H. Jack
      Lannan Foundation
      Lannan, J. Patrick
      Lansing, Charles B.
      Laurel School
      Laurence, Dean
      Lazar, Albert
      Lebron, James J.
      Lee and Co., Inc., Albert R.
      Lefebre Gallery
      Legros, M. J.
      Leighton, Kaye
      Lemmon, Cyril W.
      Lerner Publications
    - Lescaze, William - Madison, Geraldine, 1958-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 1)
      Lescaze, William
      Levin, Jeanne
      Lewis, C. McKenzie
      Lidgerwood, William V.
      Life Magazine
      Lipinsky, Lino S.
      List, Mrs. Albert
      Litchfield, Dorothy Hale
      Little Red School House ( see: Charity Exhibitions)
      Littlefield, William H.
      Living Theatre
      Lloyd, Mrs. H. Gates
      Loesser, Mrs. Arthur
      l'Oeuvre Gravée
      Long Beach Island Art Foundation
      Lord, John
      Love, Ruth Winfield
      Lucas, John and Sikie
      Lye, Ann
      Lynch, Kenneth and Sons
      MacDowell Colony
      Macomber, Connie and Pete
      Madison, Geraldine
    - Maeght, Aimé (Galerie Maeght; Maeght Editeur), 1957-1959; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Magriel, Paul - Minerva Printing Corp., 1951-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 3)
      Magriel, Paul
      Majewski, Marek
      Mandel, Samuel
      Mannes, L.
      Marble Chair Company, B. L.
      Maremont, Arnold H.
      Maringer, Carol
      Marsh and McLennan
      Marshall, Marvin V.
      Martha Jackson Gallery (see: Jackson Gallery, Martha)
      Martin Widdifield Gallery (see: Widdifield Gallery, Martin)
      Marx, Hilda
      Massie, Edward
      Massilon Museum
      Mattos, Astres
      Mayer Gallery
      Mayo Hill Colony Club
      Mayse, Purney
      McBride, Mrs. Malcolm L.
      McClellan, H. Chad
      McDonald, Dorcas
      McGee, Winston
      McGinnis, Mrs. Patrick
      McLaughlin, Charles E.
      Mead Corporation
      Mechanical Engineering
      Medusa, La
      Melamed, A.
      Mellon, Gertrude A.
      Merrill, Turben and Company, Inc.
      Metro
      Metropolitan Museum of Art
      Meyer, Carl
      Meyer, Carl F. G., IV
      Mezzalama, Francesco
      Midwestern University
      Minerva Printing Corp.
    - Minneapolis Institute of Arts - Museum of Fine Arts, Houston, 1956-1964; 1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 4)
      Minneapolis Institute of Arts
      Minnesota Mining and Manufacturing Co.
      Modernage Photographic Services
      Moderna Museet
      Molnar, Eleanor
      Molton Gallery
      Montefiore Home
      Moore, Dan T.
      Moore, George S.
      Moore, John M.
      Moore, Mrs, Paul
      Moreland, C. A.
      Morris International Gallery Limited, Jerrold
      Morris, Robert and Eleanor
      Morris, Mrs. William
      Morse, A. Reynolds
      Morton, Alastair
      Moss, Moe
      Motion Picture Association of America, Inc.
      Motive Magazine
      Mount Sinai Hospital of Cleveland
      Mount Union College
      Multiplex Display Fixture Co.
      Mundane Club
      Munro, Eleanor
      Murphy, Gerald
      Murray Co., George A.
      Musée National d'Art Moderne
      Museum of Fine Arts, Houston
    - Museum of Modern Art, 1959-1963; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 5-6)
    - Myers, Forrest - Palmer, A., 1952-1963; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 7)
      Myers, Forrest
      Nasher, Raymond D.
      Nassau, Jason
      National Conference of Christians and Jews
      National Council of Jewish Women, Inc., North Essex Section ( see: Charity Exhibitions)
      National Institute of Arts and Letters
      National Jewish Monthly
      Nelson Gallery of Art, William R.
      Neuberger, Roy
      Neuman, Eckhard
      Nevelson, Mike
      Newark Museum
      New Canaan Library Art Committee
      Newhouse, Mrs. Samuel I.
      Newman, Muriel
      Newsweek
      New York Graphic Society
      New York Herald Tribune
      New York Public Library
      New Yorker
      Night in Budapest Committee
      Nolan, Mildred
      Nordness Gallery
      Noyes, Eliot
      N. W. Ayer and Son, Inc. (see: Ayer and Son, Inc., N. W.)
      Oakwood Club
      Obata, Gyo
      Obelisco Gallery, L'
      Obelisk Gallery
      Ohio Desk Company
      Ohio Society of New York
      Ohio University
      Oliphant, Stephen D.
      Olivier, Lawrence
      Orleans Gallery
      Orswell, Lois
      Otto Gerson Gallery, Inc. (see: Gerson Gallery, Otto)
      Overton, Douglas
      Oxford University Press
      Pahlmann, William
      Palmer, A.
    - Panza, Giuseppe - Pyrotronics, 1958-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Panza, Giuseppe
      Park Crescent Hotel
      Parks, Anita Jackson
      Parsons, Betty
      Payson, Hal
      Penney, Charles
      Pennsylvania State University
      Peratt, Valentine
      Peterson, Thomas F.
      Phipps, T. J.
      Piccarello, Frank, Jr.
      Pictures on Exhibit
      Pirandello
      Polaroid Corporation
      Pollock, Lewis G.
      Pollock, Peter
      Pond, Pearl Cowles
      Poole College
      Poole, Lynn
      Portable Gallery Color Slides
      Posner, Henry, Sr.
      Print Club of Cleveland
      Print Council of America
      Pryun, Mrs. R. L.
      Purdue University
      Putnam, John B.
      PVI Gallery
      Pyrotronics
    - Rapuano, Michael - Rutgers University, 1992; 1952-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 9)
      Rapuano, Michael
      Ratner, Anne
      Rattner, Abraham
      Redfern Gallery, Ltd.
      Reichel, Miriam Brudno
      Reichold, Henry H.
      Relph, Grace
      Revel Travel Service
      Reynolds, R. S., Jr.
      Richards, Meryl
      Richelle Gallery
      Rillison, Mrs. Lawrence
      Rindler, L. A.
      Ringling Museum of Art, John and Mabel
      Roanoke Fine Arts Center
      Robertson, Bryan
      Robles Gallery, Esther
      Robson, Elizabeth Stone
      Rockefeller
      Rockefeller, David
      Rockefeller Institute
      Rockefeller, Nelson A.
      Rodriguez, Marcial
      Roland deAenllie Gallery (see: deAenllie Gallery, Roland)
      Rome-New York Art Foundation, Inc.
      Rose Fried Gallery (see: Fried Gallery, Rose)
      Rosen, Israel
      Rosenberg, Mrs. Edwin
      Rosenthal, Arthur J.
      Rothstsein, Anna
      Rowfant Club
      R. Scherer, Inc. (see: Scherer Inc., R.)
      Rubin, William S.
      Rubinfield, Donald
      Russell, Alfred
      Rutgers University
    - Sachs Gallery, A. M. - Segy Gallery, 1949-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 10)
      Sachs Gallery, A. M.
      Saidenberg, Eleanor
      Saint Mary's College
      St. Moritz Hotel
      Salant, Mrs. Walter
      Salon de Mai
      Salt Lake City Public Library
      Saltonstall, Nathaniel
      Sampliner, Mrs. Paul
      Sanborn, William E.
      Sandbert, W.
      Santa Barbara Museum of Art
      Sarnoff, Robert
      Saturday Review
      Scaife, Richard M.
      Schaefer Gallery, Bertha
      Scherer Inc., R.
      Schermerhorn Gallery
      Schloss, Charles M.
      Schmalenbach, Werner
      Schmeller, Alfred
      Schmitt, Dorothy
      Schofield, Barbara
      School Art League
      Schreiber, Taft B.
      Schultz, Olga
      Schultz Roofing, P. W.
      Schwartz, Charles
      Scientific American
      Seattle Post Intelligencer
      Segal, Walter
      Seglen, Philip M.
      Segrestan, Mrs. Jacque
      Segy Gallery
    - Seiberling, J. Fred - Speyer, Darthea, 1957-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 11)
      Seiberling, J. Fred
      Selby, Lynn
      Selden, George
      Seuphon, Michel
      Seymour, William and Florence
      Shaker Heights City School District
      Shaker Square Travel Service
      Sheldon, Albert M.
      Shestack, M. M.
      Short Run Color Corporation
      Show Magazine
      Sidney Janis Gallery (see: Janis Gallery, Sidney)
      Siff, Aida d'Agostino
      Singer, Mrs. Albert
      Singer Company
      Skidmore College
      Skidmore, Owings and Merrill
      Skowhegan School of Painting and Sculpture
      Sloan Gallery of American Painting
      Sloss, Lily
      Smith, C. Lee, Jr.
      Smith, D. C.
      Smith, Frank F.
      Smith, Ray
      Smoluchowski, Roman
      Society for the Advancement of Judaism
      Society of Gourmets for the Leisure Arts, Inc.
      Solinger, David M. and Hope
      Soltz, Al
      Southern Illinois University
      Special Surveys
      Sperling, Mrs. Milton
      Sperry, Victoria
      Speyer, Darthea
    - Spock, Benjamin - Syracuse University, 1957-1964; 1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 12)
      Spock, Benjamin
      Springger-Penquin Company
      Sprinzen, Harold
      Stable Gallery
      Staempfeli Gallery, Inc.
      Stamford Jewish Center
      State Teachers College (Slippery Rock, Pa.)
      State University College (Fredonia, N. Y.)
      State University of Iowa
      Staten Island Institute of Arts and Sciences
      Stedelijk van Abbemuseum Eindhoven
      Stein, Ronald
      Steinberg, Saul
      Stewart, Sam E.
      Stillman, Rufus C.
      Stockton, Robert S. and Ann
      Stone Gallery, Allan
      Stone, David C.
      Stone, Morton J.
      Stowe Area Association, Inc.
      Strauss, Marion
      Streitmann, A. P.
      Stroup, Beatrice Moore
      Strub, Henry
      Studio Magazine
      Suburban Temple Women's Committee
      Swarthmore College
      Sweeney, James Johnson
      Sylvester, Edmund
      Syracuse University
    - Takis, Vassilakis, 1975-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Tanager Gallery - United States Steel Corporation, 1950-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 14)
      Tanager Gallery
      Tangerman, R. S.
      Tannhauser, Justin
      Tate Gallery
      Tatelbaum, Harriet
      Taylor, Jay
      Taylor, Elizabeth
      Taylor, William and Jean
      Techbuilt, Inc.
      Temple
      Temple B'nai Sholom ( see: Charity Exhibitions)
      Temple Emanuel
      Ten Thirty Gallery
      Tenenbaum, Frieda
      Thibaut Gallery
      Tiffany and Co.
      Tile Classics
      Tishman, Robert V.
      Titelman, Mrs. Frank M.
      Toledo Museum of Art
      Tooth and Sons, Ltd., Arthur
      Tower Fellowship
      Tower Press
      Tremco Manufacturing Company
      Trenton State College
      Trigg, Ernest T.
      True Magazine
      Tudor, Charles
      Tudor Publishing Co.
      Turn Toward Peace ( see: Charity Exhibitions)
      Tuttie, Irwin and Nancy
      Twentieth Century Gallery
      Tyson Operating Company, Inc.
      Ullman, A. James
      UNICEF
      Uniontown Friends of Art Committee
      United Air Lines
      United Appeal of Greater Cleveland
      United Jewish Appeal of Greater New York
      United Palestine Appeal
      United States Customs
      United States Department of Commerce
      United States Information Agency
      United States Post Office
      United States Steel Corporation
    - University of Alabama - Waldorf, Dorothy Densmore, 1957-1964; 1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 15)
      University of Alabama
      University of Illinois
      University of Maryland
      University of Massachusetts
      University of Michigan
      University of Minnesota
      University of Pennsylvania
      University of Pittsburgh
      University of St. Thomas
      University of Southern Illinois
      University of Washington
      University School Alumni Association
      Vaiksnoras, Anthony J.
      Van der Beek, Stan
      Van der Marck, Jan H.
      Van Dyke, J. Brooks
      Vanik, Charles A.
      Venice Bienale
      Verlag M. Dumont Schauberg
      Village Voice
      Viviano, Catherine
      Vocational Guidance and Rehabilitation Services
      Vogel, Amos
      Waddington Galleries
      Wade, Jeptha H.
      Wake Forest College
      Walden School
      Waldhorns Interiors
      Waldorf, Dorothy Densmore
    - Walker Art Center, 1958-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 16-17)
    - Walkup, Park E. - Western Adjustment and Inspection Co., 1951-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 18)
      Walkup, Park E.
      Wallace, Sylvia C.
      Walling, Hayden
      Walter Landor and Associates (see: Landor and Associates, Walter)
      Ware, Paul and Betty
      Warwick and Legler, Inc. Advertising
      Wayne, June
      WDOK Radio
      Wise, Samuel D.
      Webb Chapter No. 14, Royal Arch Masons
      Weber, John
      Weese, Harry
      Weidler, Charlotte
      Weidlinger, Madeleine
      Weil, Freddie and Ann
      Weil, Eilene
      Weil, Helen L.
      Weil, R. K.
      Weil, Walter
      Weill, Guy and Lucy
      Weis, David and Jeanette
      Weisman, Fred
      Wellesley College
      Welton, Karlyn
      Wengroth, Richard A.
      Wenstrup, Margaret
      WERE Radio
      West Village Committee
      Westbury Hotel
      Western Adjustment and Inspection Co.
    - Western Reserve University, Archival Resource Key (Box 2)
      - Advisory Committee on Music (re: affiliation with Cleveland Institute of Music), 1952-1953; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 19)
      - Correspondence with President John S. Millis and Others (Howard Wise, Trustee), 1951-1963; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 20)
      - "Looking at Modern Art" (study/discussion course held at Howard Wise Gallery), 1958-1959; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - Visiting Committee on Visual Arts, 1957-1959; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Westlake Plastics Co. - Wofford College, 1957-1966; 1984-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 23)
      Westlake Plastics Co.
      Weston, S. Burns
      Westport Community Art Association
      Weyhe Gallery
      White, John F.
      Whitney Museum of American Art
      Wick, Kenneth B.
      Wickham, Ben
      Widdifield Gallery, Martin
      Wildenstein Gallery
      Wilder, Nicholas
      Wildwood, Camp
      Wilkinson, Kirk
      Willard Gallery
      William R. Nelson Gallery of Art (see: Nelson Gallery of Art, William R.)
      Williams, Kay
      Williams, Oscar
      Wilson, Ralph
      Winton, D. Mike
      Wise, John
      Wise, Victor
      Wittenberg Public Relations, Ernest
      Wixom, Nancy
      WNET-TV
      Woehle, Fritz
      Wofford College
    - Women's City Club of Cleveland, 1958-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Wood, Remsen - Zimmerman, Mrs. Isadore J., 1957-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 25)
      Wood, Remsen
      Woodward Foundation
      Woody, Russell O., Jr.
      Woollen, Evans
      Worcester Art Museum
      Worcester Foundation for Experimental Biology
      World House Galleries
      WPAT Radio
      Wragge, Sydney
      Wurtzburger, Alan
      Wurzburger, Paul D.
      York, Scott R.
      Yoseido Gallery
      Young, Stephen M.
      Zabriskie Gallery
      Zadok, Charles
      Zanini, Walter
      Zegman, Freda
      Zero-Max Industries, Incorporated
      Zimmerman, Mrs. Isadore J.
  - New York Gallery Correspondence, 1962-1970; 1984; 1.2; Archival Resource Key
    This subseries consists of the correspondence of Howard Wise, several gallery employees, and art consultant Douglas MacAgy, and documents the operations and activities of Howard Wise Gallery, New York. A 1970 letter from Wise addressed "to the friends of the gallery" announces the closing of the gallery. A draft of a 1984 letter reflecting on the 1969 exhibition TV as a Creative Medium is also found.
    - New York Gallery Correspondence, 1984; 1962-1965; 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 25-28)
- Artist Files, 1950-1984; Series 2; Archival Resource Key; 3.4 Linear feet Boxes 3-6
  Most artists represented in this series were affiliated with Howard Wise Gallery either in Cleveland or New York City, but some files are for individuals of possible interest to the gallery, or document Wise's continued contact with artists after the Howard Wise Gallery closed. Files contain varying combinations of correspondence, printed material, notes, writings, and photographs.
  Files are arranged alphabetically by artist name.
  - Aach, Herbert, 1960-1967, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Abend, George, 1950-1964, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Afro (Basaldella), 1957, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Ahr, Dick, 1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Aldcroft, Richard, 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Altamura, Frank P., 1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Altman, Harold, 1959-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Armitage, Kenneth, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Barker, Walter, 1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Barnet, Will, 1958-1959; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Barr, Norman, 1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Barré, Martin and Martine, 1957-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Barry, Carver S., 1958; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Bayer, Herbert, 1957-1965, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 14-15)
  - Bayliss, George, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Bell, Trevor, 1962, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Benton, Fletcher, 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Bergman, Anna Eva, 1958; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Bergschneider, John, 1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Bernstein, Sylvia, 1959; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Berrocal, Miguel, 1958; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Bertrand, Huguette-Arthur, 1957-1963, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Bertschmann, Harry, 1957-1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Bhandt, Cort Leigh, 1958; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Birch, James A., 1959; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Bird, G., 1958; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Blake, John, 1963; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Blielfield, Stanley, 1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Blow, Sandra, 1958, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Bolomey, R. H., 1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Bookatz, Samuel, 1959; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Booth, Cameron, 1961-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Brainard, Owen, 1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Braque, Georges, 1958; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Brenson, Theodore, 1958-1959; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Briggs, Ernest, 1954-1964, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 37-38)
  - Brose, Morris, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Brown, Milton, 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Buggiani, Paolo, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Burlin, Paul, 1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Cajori, Charles, 1961-1965, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Calcagno, Lawrence, 1958-1959; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Campitelli, Russell, 1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Casarella, Edmond, 1957-1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Cash, James G., undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Celentano, Francis, 1964-1967, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Chagall, Marc, 1957-1960, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Chesini, Sergio Dino, 1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Christoforou, 1960-1961, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Citron, Mina, 1956-1959; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Clark, Ed, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Cook, Sally, 1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Corneille, 1953-1961, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Cox, J. Halley, 1959; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Cramer, Belle, 1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Crawford, Ralston, 1959; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Crehan, Hubert, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Davidson, Morris, 1959-1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Davis, Gene, 1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Day, Worden, 1959-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - de Botto, Jean, 1958-1959; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - de Kooning, Elaine, 1959-1961, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - de Martelli, John, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - De Soto, Ernest, 1957-1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Dininno, Frank A., 1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Domato, Hisao, 1957; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Dominat, Paul, 1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Donahue, George, 1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Drew, Joan, 1958; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Drew, Ray, 1959; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Dugmore, Edward, 1954-1963, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Dumitresco, Natalia, 1958-1962, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Eckhardt, Edris, 1958-1961, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Edwards, Ethel, 1957-1961, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Elliott, Stanley B., 1967-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Erlanger, Elizabeth N., 1959; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Erol (Akayavash), 1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Feeley, Paul, 1957; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - Ferber, Herbert, 1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - Ferren, John, 1959-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - Fieto, Luis, 1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 83)
  - Fine, Perle, 1959-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 84)
  - Fogel, Seymour, 1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 85)
  - Fontana, Lucio, 1964-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 86)
  - Forndran, Werner, 1956; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 87)
  - Fraenkel, Richard, 1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 88)
  - Francken, Ruth, 1956-1962, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 89)
  - Frank, Emily, 1962; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 90)
  - Frasconi, Antonio, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 91)
  - Freimark, Robert M., 1958; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 92)
  - Frost, Terry, 1958-1962, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 93)
  - Gardner, Joan Andrews, 1957; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 94)
  - Garelli, Franco, 1958-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 95)
  - Gaudneck, Walter, 1960-1965,undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 96)
  - Gauguin, Tom, 1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 97)
  - Geist, Stanley, 1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 98)
  - Gemberling, Kathleen, 1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 99)